The invocation by the Minister of the Parts of the Church, Mr. Brandon Fudger.
Please, Bill.
Father God, we love you. God, I'm grateful to be a part of a community that has so many people who are passionate, passionate about local business and growth, and just having the best place available to live.
God, I pray that tonight, anything disgusting to the decisions that are made that all of it is to just further the growth here and further your glory.
God, with election season, we know there's important decisions to be made tomorrow, and we just pray that your will would be carried out.
God, and everything, we love you. We thank you for the gifts that you've given us, and we just ask that we would be able to live a life worthy of you.
I help us to be more like Jesus, as soon as then we pray. Amen.
Amen.
On four public input, or unscheduled personal appearances, five consent agenda staff recommends we approve out of six and seven.
All right. Now we will make motion to approve the meets on Crete, PO23-01-781.
I'll make the motion to approve.
All right.
Eight.
A word contract agreements to refill the services, still environmental services, and B3
construction for solicitation.
Number Q23-08, bid for tipping fees, transportation fees, for solid waste disposal,
contingent upon the submission of all required contract documents, and approve city
manager or his designated sign, notice to proceed.
Mr. Brown, rest of it.
Thank you.
Okay, so you rebate or be
And the hand that we know they were looking at through the massage room
It's clear
And
That was pretty clear
Yeah
I don't know
I don't know that got a warm picture
Fortunately some of these pictures
To do that
Feel like it's been all done
Just carry a laying out there to use
That's pretty clear
That's right, so what's going to happen?
Or we'll haul it.
Yeah.
What are you saying?
The demo we would haul ourselves to.
All right.
Number nine.
Other new business of any, which is a business of forcing this agenda.
10 staff reports.
11 trustee community announcement.
12.
This meeting will be continued from Councillor Chambers,
reconvened the staff room for the purpose of executive session as a completion.
I mean, the agenda item five of the regular meeting of the Mama,
Industrial Public Facilities Authority.